# Hadi Lashkari Ghouchani

## **Android Developer**

@ hadi.pro.dev@gmail.com

+34 645 86 91 03

Parcelona, Spain in linkedin.com/in/hadilg

github.com/hadilq

M medium.com/@hadilq.dev

#### **Summary**

A curious developer with over 15 years of experience in software development, where almost 5 years of his experience covers Android development, over 2 years covers teaching algorithms and programming in universities, and over 8 years covers academic and self-employed experiences while he was a student.

An Introvert person who has profound learning and contributing skills. A creative, value driven and passionate developer who enjoys doing math, solving problems and creating scalable, maintainable, testable and efficient apps to make the world a better place to live.

A person whose goal is to surround himself with happy, creative, motivative and clever persons, so his talent becomes flourished

He's interested in Data Science, Machine Learning, Functional Programming, Differentiable Programming, Category Theory, Math, etc. so constantly looking forward to learning related technologies to use in Mobile apps

### **Experience**

### Senior Android Developer

at Letgo

🛗 Oct. 2019 - Present

Barcelona, Spain

Letgo is the biggest classified marketplace in Turkey with 15+ million apps installed on Android devices alone.

#### Mission:

- Fix a couple of bugs and implement multiple features and their A/B Testing
- Working on variants of Search Alert Entry Points
- Improve the performance of loading feeds by at least a minute
- · Fix multiple Memory leaks
- Known as "The man who broke the escape room" to emphasize his ability to think out of the box

#### Technologies:

- · Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Room, etc
- · Agile, Sprint, Github Flow, CI/CD, Dynamic Feature Module Delivery
- Mockito, Espresso, Robolectric, Jacoco, Ktlint, Fastlane
- Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Figma
- New Relic, Firebase, Amplitude, Leanplum, etc.

#### Lead Android Developer

at Sheypoor

🛗 Jan. 2018 - Jan. 2019

O Tehran, Iran

Sheypoor is one of two lead classified marketplaces in Iran with 1.5+ million users per day, 13+ million overall users and 344+ million sessions.

#### Missions

- Increase the number of users per day from 0.5+ million to 1.5+ million in a year.
- As functional manager of the Android team, he was responsible for the code quality of the Sheypoor app. He coached the team to practice design patterns, clean code, and using app architecture, along with updating libraries and adding new features with focus on agility and UX.
- · Implementing new design of the entire app, including rebranding for summer campaign
- · Improving the legacy code quality by adding Dagger and Kotlin.

- Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Butter Knife, Greendao, etc.
- Agile, Kanban, Git Flow, CI/CD
- Mockito, Espresso, Jacoco
- Pivotal Tracker, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Zeplin, etc

## Senior Android Developer

at Myket

🛗 Sep. 2015 - Des. 2017

O Tehran, Iran

Myket is one of two lead app stores in Iran with over 8+ million users.

- Starting TDD and installing Jenking's pipeline to handle CI/CD.
- Implementing features such as handling deeplinks, search page, inbox page, etc.

## Technologies:

- Dagger 2, Volley, OneSignal, EventBus, OrmLite, etc.
- · Agile, Scrum, Git Flow
- · Mockito, Espresso
- · Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Gitlab, Jfrog, Jenkins

## Java and C# developer

at Soha System

mar. 2015 - Aug. 2015

Tehran, Iran

SOHA is formed to focus on solutions based on smart cards.

## Missions:

- Implementing RFID card reader Android app via bluetooth connection.
- Implementing Android and desktop apps.

## Lecturer

at Universities

m Feb. 2012 - Dec. 2014

Mashhad, Iran

After two years of enrollment by conscription, he had been starting his work in two universities, Payame Noor University and Sadjad University of Technology.

## Courses Taught:

Application of Computers in Physics, Mathematical Physics, etc.

## **Article / Repository**

- 🔿 2020 Sample App: Provide a full implementation for a No-Framework Dependency Injection in Kotlin.
- $\bigcirc$  2020 Contributing on  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  2020 Contributing on  $\triangle$  2020 Contributing on  $\triangle$  2020 Contributing on  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  2020 Contributing on  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Contributing on  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$  100 Contributing on  $\triangle$  100 Library:  $\triangle$
- 2020 Library: A Kotlin compiler plugin that generates trackable method
- 1 2020 Medium post: Save State By Using RxJava or Kotlin Flow 2020 Medium post: RxJava instead of LiveData in MVVM
- 2020 Library: A glue between the lifecycle of LifecycleOwner in Android and upstreams in RxJava

- 2019 Sample App: Functional Programming + Clean Architecture
- ↑ 2019 Sample App: Movie Challenge
  ↑ 2019 Math Library: Modularized, mathematical and multiplatform Kotlin library
  1 2018 ProAndroidDev post: Logging in Kotlin
- 2018 Sample App: Clean Architecture + RMVVM
- 1 2018 ProAndroidDev post: Loading entities from database and server API by using RxJava 2018 ProAndroidDev post: LiveData with single events
- 2018 LiveEvent library: It's useful to propagate single event to View

## Education

Sharif University Of Technology Payame Noor University

M.Sc B.Sc in Physics

in Physics

🛗 Jul. 2007

O Tehran, Iran Mashhad, Iran

### **Tools / Skills**

#### Android

Lifecycles/LiveData/Navigation/Paging/ViewModel Multidex/Test/Data Binding/WorkManager/Room Android Architecture Components/JetPack Dagger 2/RxJava 2/Retrofit 2/.. Kotlin Multiplatform/Kotlin Coroutines Kotlin Compiler Plugin/. View Binding/Butter Knife/ObjectBox/...

#### **Architecture**

Clean Architecture/Hexagonal Architecture Unidirectional data flow Architecture MVVM/MVI/MVP/RMVVM

#### Principle

Clean Code/SOLID Object Oriented Programming Functional Programming Stable Dependencies Principle Stable Abstractions Principle

#### Design Pattern

Factory/Builder/Singleton/.. Adapter/Facade/Proxy/Visitor/... Strategy/Chain of responsibility/..

## Android test library

JUnit/Mockito/Espresso/Jacoco/...

#### **Build Tool**

Gradle/Sbt/Maven/Ant/Make/...

#### Command Line Tool

grep/sed/netstat/awk/docker/.. adb/sdkmanager/avdmanager/...

#### **Development Tool**

Pivotal Tracker/Jira/Jenkins/Travis/CircleCi/...

#### **Programing Language**

Java/Kotlin/Scala/Haskell/Python Groovy/Dart/Javascript/Rust/..

Linux(Fedora/Ubuntu/Debian), OS X

## Operating System

- **Special Honor**
- 2019 Had an offer from Kik, Kitechener, Canada 2019 Had an offer from Letgo, Barcelona, Spain
- 2019 Had an offer from CRITICAL Techworks, BMW, Porto,
- Portugal 2019 Had an offer from The Next Big Thing, Berlin, Ger-
- 2018 Received result-oriented badge in Sheypoor 2007 Ranked 44th among more than five thousand participants in the National Graduate Entrance Exam in

## Language

English: Advance Farsi: Native

The source of this resume in github Built at August 6, 2020